kosmix.com 2010-12-04

# Privacy Policy on Kosmix

_RightHealth is owned and operated by Kosmix.View Kosmix's Terms of Service._

This is the privacy policy (the " **Privacy Policy** ") for all websites owned and made available by Kosmix Corporation (" **Kosmix** ") including, without limitation, the website you are on now (collectively, the " **Site** "). We respect your privacy and appreciate the confidence you have placed in the Site. We are committed to protecting your privacy and preserving your trust. Please carefully review this Privacy Policy to learn about how we collect, use and protect any Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) you provide us on or through the Site and your choices for managing your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Service posted on the Site.

## Opting Out Of Future Communications; Updating And Deleting Personal Information

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to exclude your Personal Information from our direct marketing purposes, please tell us so at:

> Kosmix Corporation   
> 444 Castro Street, Suite 700   
> Mountain View, CA 94041   
> ph: 650-938-2300   
> fax: 650-938-5959   
> email: [legal@kosmix.com](mailto:legal@kosmix.com)

If you would like to update or delete your e-mail address, mailing address or other Personal Information with us please contact us the same way.

## Information We Automatically Collect

We automatically collect information that does not reflect or reference an individually identifiable user (" **Non-Personal Information** ") to help us understand how our users use the Site. For example, each time you use the Site we automatically collect your IP address and other information about your Internet connectivity. In addition, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a string of characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your Web browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Certain of our Service Providers (defined below) may use cookies in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.

## Information You Choose To Submit

We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information (" **Personal Information** ") only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information to register with the Site, subscribe to one of our services, enter sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in certain areas of the Site.

## How Do We Use, And When Do We Share, Personal and Non-Personal Information We Collect?

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect information when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this Site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you.. These companies may also place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with serving ads and/or collecting information about your visit to the Site. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party advertising company may collect from you.

We will not sell, share or rent Personal Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours (" **Service Providers** "). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services including credit card processing, data management, promotional services, Web hosting, Web development, etc. We provide our service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your Personal Information when we have reason to believe it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Kosmix, to its affiliates or to others. We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe the law requires it.

We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain aggregated Non-Personal Information (e.g., the number of users who searched for a particular term, how many users clicked on a particular advertisement, the number of users who reside in a particular geographic location, etc.) without your permission. However, such information does not identify you individually.

## Security

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through Site, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site, and you do so at your own risk.

## Third Party Website Links And Content

The Site may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked websites or third party content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked website before disclosing any information on such site.

## E-mail Newsletters/Services

We may send you e-mails regarding Kosmix, the Site or a special promotion or event. All such e-mails contain an opt-out mechanism if you do not wish to receive future e-mails from us.

## Children's Privacy Statement

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a user under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

## Policy Changes

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting the changed Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the Effective Date disclosed in the changed Privacy Policy. The new Privacy Policy will apply to all current and past users of the Site and will replace any prior Privacy Policies that are inconsistent.

Effective Date: 2/1/2008
